<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>aero/astro on delia stephens</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/aeroastro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in aero/astro on delia stephens</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/aeroastro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fault Injector</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/aeroastro/fault-injector/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/aeroastro/fault-injector/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-overview&#34;&gt;Project Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Testing UAVs in the field can be costly: not only must you charge batteries, go through checklists, prepare the drone, transport people and materials to the testing site, and return everything to its place, there is the chance that the changes you have made will fail. Software-in-the-loop (&lt;a href=&#34;http://ardupilot.org/dev/docs/sitl-simulator-software-in-the-loop.html&#34;&gt;SITL&lt;/a&gt;) simulation eliminates the need for physical tests but maintains the integrity of the testing environment by linking a flight dynamics model such as &lt;a href=&#34;http://jsbsim.sourceforge.net/&#34;&gt;JSBSim&lt;/a&gt; to the autopilot, enabling rapid development and testing of UAV software.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAJA</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/aeroastro/maja/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/aeroastro/maja/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-overview&#34;&gt;Project Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During Summer 2019, while working at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cicataqro.ipn.mx/cq/qro/Paginas/../index.html&#34;&gt;CICATA&lt;/a&gt;, I was tasked with desiging a flight program to train people on the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bormatec.com/produkte&#34;&gt;Bormatec MAJA&lt;/a&gt;, a long-range UAV designed to hold large payloads for aerial surveillance. In addition to desiging checklists and flight logs, I created a model of the drone for use in PhoenixRC, a now-defunct flight simulator that the program had readily available.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While a more detailed description of the process I used is available in Gist format &lt;a href=&#34;https://gist.github.com/deliastephens/a7144b50509f97a37b59a5e540ffdf5c&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, below is a brief overview of what I accomplished over the course of a couple of weeks over the summer. I went from only baseline modeling experience to relative proficiency, producing a model that is similar in appearance and functionality to the Bormatec MAJA.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
